

Nguyễn MINH CHÍ

Front End Developer

Date of birth: Feb 1, 1997

Gender: Male

Phone: 0349932192

Email: nmchiht@gmail.com

Address: 313B Trần Hưng Đạo Đông Hòa Dĩ An Bình Dương

Website: https://www.facebook.com/baron0124/

OBJECTIVE

Take advantage of your existing skills and experience, learn new skills and technologies to become an expert in the near future, bringing a lot of value to your partner as well as your own development. From there, I will contribute to the development of the Company.

EDUCATION

DEC 2015 - NOV 2021

Thai Nguyen University of Information and Communication

Technology

Major: Information Technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2023 - Present

FINANTAGED

Front End Developer Website Finantaged

- Build website on ReactJs, NextJs, Wordpress
- Technology: Reactjs, react-redux, Scss
- Tools: Figma
- Build website interface based on existing designs
- Product implementation and operation to improve and upgrade new

features.

- Fix bug

May 2022 - Present

PROJECT

Front End Developer

Website Portfolio

- Build website on ReactJs, Nextjs
- Technology: Reactjs, react-redux, Tailwind Css
- Link demo: https://bnportfolio.vercel.app/

May 2022 - Present

FREELANCER

Front End Developer

Website GasCongNghiep

Website GreenHouse

- Build website on Wordpress
- Deploy system in Linux
- Fix bugs

Jul 2021 - Jan 2022

VANO JSC

Front End Developer

Vano is a Vietnamese company, along with more than 10 years of experience in the business of content and communication services on mobile telecommunications networks. Currently, VANO is cooperating with many major media partners (Viettel, Vinaphone, Mobifone) and partners providing copyrighted, experienced, and reputable content in the Vietnamese market.

- Monitor, manage, control deployed websites, landing pages.
- Monitor the process of product implementation and operation to improve and upgrade new features.
- Build website on Wordpress
- Deploy system in Linux
- Fix bugs

CERTIFICATIONS

2020 Bachelor of Information Technology from FPT APTECH

SKILLS

Technologies	Reactjs, Nextjs, Nuxtjs, Tailwind CSS, Laravel, Wordpress, Bootstrap, PHP, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, Java Spring Boot
Database	MySQL, MongoDB
Tools	Github, Bitbucket, MobaXterm, Gitlab
Language	English: Basic writing and reading
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint

PROJECTS

Beauty'l

(Aug 2023 - Current)

Customer	Finantaged
Description	Service of providing information content on telecommunications network for customers using MobiFone subscribers
Team size	1
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- Wordpress - MySQL

Finantaged

(Apr 2023 - Current)

Customer	Finantaged
Description	Gateway to financial freedom in the fast-paced world of the financial services industry
Team size	4
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Bug Fixing

Technologies used	- Reactjs, Nextjs	T
	- MySQL	

Portfolio

(2022 - Current)

Customer	Myself
Description	Introducing personal experiences and experiences, projects and technologies used
Team size	1
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- Nextjs, Reactjs, Tailwind CSS

SucKhoeHot

(Mar 2022 - Current)

Customer	Vinvas
Description	Channel of information about health, life tips
Team size	2
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- Wordpress - MySQL

DauGialbid

(Nov 2021 - Current)

Customer	Vano
Description	Service of providing information content on telecommunications network for customers using MobiFone subscribers
Team size	2
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- Laravel - MySQL

Vano

(Apr 2022 - Current)

Customer	Vano
Description	Website copany
Team size	1
My position	Website operation, Frontend developer
My responsibilities	- Development - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- Wordpress - MySQL